A Guide to the American Lung Association of Virginia (ALAV) Collection
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- SOUTHERN TUBERCULOSIS CONFERENCE BY ROGER SCHMIDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: JOHN COLLINS, ET AL., 1967-1968, 17-D, 17-N, 9-TL, 6-TLS, 2-pam, 1-DS (Box-folder 181:008)
- SOUTHERN TB CONFERENCE BY ALICE PORTER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1966-1967, 10-D, 3-pam, 1-TLS, 2-N (Box-folder 181:009)
- SOUTHERN TUBERULOSIS CONFERENCE BY JOHN COLLINS, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1965-1966, 16-D, 6-TLS, 7-TL, 5-N, 1-pam, 2-c.d.s (Box-folder 181:010)
- SOUTHERN TUBERCULOSIS CONFERENCE BY FRED BROECKER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: JUDSON ALLRED, JR., ET AL., 1963-1964, 26-D, 1-AD, 36-TL, 18-TLS, 11-N, 3-ALS, 1-ANS, 1-AN,1-D (Box-folder 181:011)
- SOUTHERN TUBERCULOSIS CONFERENCE BY ALBERT FOSTER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1963-1964, 12-D, 8-TLS, 8-N, 2-TL (Box-folder 182:001)
- SOUTHERN TUBERCULOSIS CONFERENCE BY ALBERT FOSTER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: MEMBERS OF THE COMMITTEE, ET AL., 1963, 15-D, 11-TLS, 14-TL, 6-N, 1-c.d.s. (Box-folder 182:002)
- SOUTHERN TUBERCULOSIS CONFERENCE BY CATHARINE ZAHAROV, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: C. SCOTT VENABLE, ET AL., 1962, 35-D, 13-N, 26-TLS, 30-TL, 2-ALS, 1-pam (Box-folder 182:003)
- SOUTHERN TUBERCULOSIS CONFERENCE BY LOUISE BAGLEY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: H. BROWN WALLACE, ET AL., 1960-1961, 13-D, 12-TL, 10-TLS, 4-N, 2-NEWSCLIPS (Box-folder 182:004)
- NORA SPENCER HANMER, SOUTHERN CONFERENCE AWARD, 1959, 3-D, 1-N, 3-TLS, 3-TL (Box-folder 182:005)
- SOUTHERN TUBERCULOSIS CONFERENCE BY W.W. WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: FILE, ET AL., 1956-1959, 13-N, 8-TLS, 34-D, 12-TL, 2-NEWSCLIPS, 1-pam, 1-AD (Box-folder 182:006)
- SOUTHERN TUBERCULOSIS CONFERENCE BY HAROLD MCGEE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: J. IRVIN NICHOLS, ET AL., 1954-1955, 11-TL, 5-TLS, 6-D, 1-ANS, 3-N (Box-folder 182:007)
- SOUTHERN TUBERCULOSIS CONFERENCE BY BRYAN WILSON, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: STATE SECRETARIES, ET AL., 1952-1954, 15-D, 1-pam, 15-N, 4-TLS, 2-TL, 1-AD (Box-folder 182:008)
- SOUTHERN TUBERCULOSIS CONFERENCE BY EDWARD MCGAVRAN, ET AL., 1951, 13-D, 3-TL, 3-TLS, 5-N, 1-pam (Box-folder 182:009)
- SOUTHERN TUBERCULOSIS CONFERENCE BY J.P. KRENZ, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: STATE EXECUTIVES, ET AL., 1920-1950, 6-pam, 44-D, 19-N, 17-TLS, 13-TL, 5-NEWSCLIPS, 1-AN (Box-folder 183:001)
- SOUTHERN TUBERCULOSIS CONFERENCE BY REHABILITATION DIRECTOR, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: MRS. R.A. LAWRENCE, ET AL., 1920-1950, 34-D, 3-N, 1-AD, 31-TLS, 1-NEWSCLIP, 2-ALS, 23-TL (Box-folder 183:002)
- SOUTHERN TUBERCULOSIS CONFERENCE BY DANIEL MCCARTHY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: LESLIE FOSTER ET AL., 1920-1950, 1-N, 1-DS, 1-NEWSCLIP, 36-D, 32-TL, 54-TLS (Box-folder 183:003)
- SPEECHES--ROBERT BARRIE BY ROBERT BARRIE, 1953-1954, 21-D (Box-folder 183:004)
- SPEECHES BY D.N. ANDERSON, ET AL., 1965, 11-D (Box-folder 183:005)
  AIR POLLUTION, REHABILITATION PROGRAMS, HISTORY OF TUBERCULOSIS
- SPEECHES BY ROSS L. MCCLEAN, ET AL., 1964, 1-TL, 4-TLS, 29-D (Box-folder 184:001)
  POVERTY, HEALTH, AND COMMUNITY ACTION, FIGHTING TUBERCULOSIS, AIR POLLUTION, ROLE OF HEALTH DEPARTMENT
- SPEECHES BY MRS. MARTY MANN, ET AL., 1952-1953, 2-TLS, 1-TL, 16-D, 1-AN (Box-folder 184:002)
- SPECIAL REVENUE COMMITTEE BY THOMAS PICKNEY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: B.M. BECKHAM, JR., ET AL., 1954-1955, 2-TL (Box-folder 184:003)
- SPILMAN, DAVID L. COMPANY BY W.W. WENDT,ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: DAVID L. SPILMAN, ET AL., 1975-1977, 3-TL, 5-TLS, 5-D (Box-folder 184:004)
- STAFF DEVELOPMENT BY VLA, 1979-1981, 18-D, 6-N (Box-folder 184:005)
- STAFF DEVELOPMENT BY VLA, 1978-1979, 6-D (Box-folder 184:006)
- STAFF BY TAYLOR COPPING, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: MEMBERS OF VLA STAFF, ET AL., 1980-1981, 11-N, 2-D (Box-folder 184:007)
- STAFF DEVELOPMENT BY VLA, 1977-1978, 17-D, 2-pam, 3-N (Box-folder 184:008)
- STAFF DEVELOPMENT BY VTRDA, 1971-1977, 11-D (Box-folder 184:009)
- STAFFORD, FRANK B., M.D. BY W.W. WENDT, ET AL/ADDRESSED TO: FRANK STAFFORD, ET AL., 1955-1961, 9-ALS, 8-TL, 2-D, 1-N, 1-NEWSCLIP (Box-folder 184:010)
- STEPHENSON, MS. RUTH BRADLEY--ESTATE OF BY PHILIP J. BAGLEY, III, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: TAYLOR COPPING, ET AL., 1977-1979, 22-TLS, 4-D, 1-TL (Box-folder 184:011)
- STATE BOARD OF EDUCATION BY ROBERT BARRIE, ET AL., 1951-1971, 41-D, 3-N, 11-TLS, 20-TL, 2-NEWSCLIPS, 1-AN (Box-folder 185:001)
  VOCATIONAL REHABILITATION
- STATE CHARITIES AID ASSOCIATION BY ROBERT OSBORN, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: FELLOW TB CONSTITUENT, ET AL., 1953-1960, 7-TLS, 15-D, 1-pam, 3-TL, 2-N, 1-AN (Box-folder 185:002)
  CHRISTMAS SEAL SALES
- STATE CHRARITIES AID ASSOCIATIONS BY BILL MOORE, ET AL., 1952-1953, 10-D, 1-pam, 1-DS, 2-N, 1-ANS (Box-folder 185:003)
- STATE CHARITIES AID ASSOCIATIONS BY ROBERT OSBORN, ET AL., 1951-1952, 6-D, 1-AD, 6-TL, 1-ALS, 1-TLS (Box-folder 185:004)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH BY BUREAU OF TUBERCULOSIS CONTROL, ET AL., 1979-1981, 9-D, 9-TLS, 2-pam, 2-N, 5-TL (Box-folder 185:005)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH BY WILLIAM WRIGHT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: TAYLOR COPPING, ET AL., 1978-1979, 2-TLS, 1-NS, 6-D, 1-pam, 3-N, 1-TL (Box-folder 185:006)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH BY JAMES KENLEY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: TAYLOR COPPING, ET AL., 1977-1978, 1-AD, 1-DS, 2-TLS, 2-D, 4-N (Box-folder 185:007)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH BY WILLIAM APPERSON, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: J.G. MCNIEL, ET AL., 1973-1977, 18-D, 2-TL, 3-TLS, 10-N (Box-folder 185:008)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH BY WILLIAM APPERSON, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: THOMAS O. MOAK, JR., ET AL., 1970-1973, 2-TLS, 8-D, 7-N, 1-TL (Box-folder 185:009)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH BY THOMAS O. MOAK, JR., ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1969-1970, 2-N, 1-TL, 5-TLS, 12-D, 1-AD (Box-folder 186:001)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH BY WILLIAM WAGNER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: LOCAL HEALTH DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1968-1969, 5-N, 5-NEWSCLIPS, 10-D, 1-TLS, 2-TL (Box-folder 186:002)
  X-RAYS
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH BY WILLIAM WAGNER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: THOMAS O. MOAK, JR., ET AL., 1967-1968, 7-TLS, 6-N, 16-D, 3-TL (Box-folder 186:003)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH--FEDERAL TUBERCULOSIS PROJECT BY W.F. WAGNER, ET AL., 1966-1967, 24-D, 1-N, 1-TL, 1-TLS (Box-folder 186:004)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH BY WILLIAM WAGNER, ET AL., 1966-1967, 17-D, 6-TLS, 1-NEWSCLIP, 4-N, 2-TL (Box-folder 186:005)
- STATE DEPARMENT OF HEALTH, 1965-1966, 11-D, 2-TLS, 1-TL, 2-N (Box-folder 186:006)
  SANATORIUMS
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH BY LILLIAN PEYTON, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: JEAN SOUTH, ET AL., 1963-1964, 2-TL, 11-TLS, 17-D, 4-N, 1-NEWSCLIP (Box-folder 187:001)
  X-RAYS, TUBERCULOSIS
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH BY CATHERINE ZAHAROV, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ROBERT ANDERSON, ET AL., 1963-1964, 8-D, 8-TL, 4-TLS, 1-pam (Box-folder 187:002)
  NURSING AND PUBLIC HEALTH, STATISTICS AND PUBLIC HEALTH
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH BY W.F. WAGNER, ET AL., 1962-1963, 23-D, 20-TL, 6-N, 18-TLS, 1-AD (Box-folder 187:003)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH BY WILLIAM F. WAGNER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: EDWARD S. RAY, ET AL., 1961-1962, 9-N, 7-TL, 8-TLS, 27-D, 1-AD (Box-folder 187:004)
  TUBERCULIN TESTING, TREATING TUBERCULOSIS
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH--PATIENT EDUCATION PROGRAM, QUARANTINE LAW BY WILLIAM F. WAGNER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: LOCAL HEALTH DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1960-1961, 3-N (Box-folder 187:005)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH, PATIENT EDUCATION PROGRAM BY LUCILLE BROWNELL, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: LILLIAM PEYTON, ET AL., 1958-1959, 1-TL, 1-D (Box-folder 187:006)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH BY U.S. DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH, ET AL., 1957-1958, 10-D, 12-N, 1-AD, 1-pam, 4-TLS, 3-TL, 2-AD, 1-photo (Box-folder 187:007)
  PAYMENT FOR SANATORIUM CARE, X-RAYS, QUARANTINE LAW, NURSING
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH--REGIONAL CHEST CLINICS BY VTA, ET AL., 1956-1957, 13-D (Box-folder 187:008)
  CHEST CLINICS, MICONCEPTIONS ABOUT TUBERCULOSIS, TREATMENT OF TUBERCULOSIS
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH BY STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH, 1956-1957, 24-D, 6-N, 4-TL, 1-TLS, 1-DS, 1-map (Box-folder 188:001)
  CHEST CLINICS
- STATE HEALTH DEPARTMENT BY W.B. CARTER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: STATE AND COUNTY HEALTH DEPARTMENTS, ET AL., 1955-1956, 1-AD, 52-D, 1-map, 6-TLS, 2-TL, 1-N (Box-folder 188:002)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH--STATISTICS FROM HEALTH DISTRICTS BY L.H. DENNY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: MRS. VARBORO, ET AL., 1956-1957, 2-map, 9-D, 4-TLS, 5-AN, 1-N (Box-folder 188:003)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH BY WILLIAM WAGNER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: S.D. STURKIE, ET AL., 1958-1959, 28-D, 1-pam, 19-TLS, 5-N, 10-TL (Box-folder 188:004)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH BY DR. MACK, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ALL LOCAL HEALTH DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1959-1960, 15-D, 19-N, 3-AN, 4-TLS, 11-TL (Box-folder 188:005)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH BY WILLIAM WAGNER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: RALPH DWORK, ET AL., 1960-1961, 10-TL, 14-D, 8-TLS, 12-N (Box-folder 189:001)
  HOSPITILIZATION, NURSING
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH BY HAROLD MCGEE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: A.L. CARSON, JR., ET AL., 1954-1955, 25-TL, 11-TLS, 36-D, 3-N, 3-NEWSCLIP (Box-folder 189:002)
- STATE DEPARTMENTS OF HEALTH BY WILLIAM WAGNER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: IRVIN CRAIG, ET AL., 1953-1954, 17-TL, 42-D, 6-TLS, 4-NEWSCLIPS, 3-N (Box-folder 189:003)
  PUBLIC HEALTH IN PRISONS
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH BY JAMES PERKINS, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ROBERT BARRIE, ET AL., 1951-1953, 17-D, 11-TL, 2-N, 9-TLS, 2-NEWSCLIPS (Box-folder 189:004)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH BY WILLIAM WAGNER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: R.W. GARNETT, ET AL., 1950, 8-D, 10-TL, 9-TLS, 2-N, 1-NEWSCLIP (Box-folder 189:005)
- STATE HEALTH DEPARTMENT, SANATORIUMS BY EXECUTIVE SECRETARY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: FRANK S. JOHNS, ET AL., 1940-1949, 28-D, 1-DS, 57-TL, 23-TLS, 15-NEWSCLIPS, 11-N, 1-pam (Box-folder 189:006)
  1-AN, 4-ALS
- STATE HEALTH DEPARTMENT, BUREAU OF TUBERCULOSIS CONTROL BY REHABILITATION DIRECTOR, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: WILLIAM WAGNER, ET AL., -1949, 15-D, 3-TLS, 13-TL (Box-folder 190:001)
- STATE HEALTH DEPARTMENT BY STATE HEALTH COMMISSIONER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: LESLIE FOSTER, ET AL., 1940-1949, 10-NEWSCLIPS, 31-D, 25-TLS, 21-TL, 15-N, 1-DS, 1-ALS (Box-folder 190:002)
- STATE HEALTH DEPARTMENT, 1930-1939, 29-D, 2-NEWSCLIPS, 38-TLS, 28-TL, 1-AN (Box-folder 190:003)
- STATE HEALTH DEPARTMENT BY ELLA PHILLIPS CRANDALL, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: AGNES RANDOLPH, ET AL., 1908-1929, 1-NEWSCLIP, 43-TLS, 27-TL, 35-D, 2-pam, 3-DS, 8-AN (Box-folder 190:004)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH--FEDERAL TUBERCULOSIS PROJECT (TUBERCULOSIS TESTING PREVALENCE STUDY) BY WILLIAM WAGNER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: JAMES MCDIARMID, ET AL., 1966-1968, 15-D, 6-TLS, 6-TL, 6-N (Box-folder 191:001)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF MENTAL HEALTH AND HOSPITALS BY CATHERINE ZAHAROV, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: HERBERT KRUEGER, ET AL., 1961-1962,1967-1968, 5-D, 2-TL (Box-folder 191:002)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF MENTAL HYGIENE AND HOSPITALS BY HELEN MUGLER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: MRS. ZAHAROV, ET AL., 1956-1960, 1-TLS, 4-D, 1-TL (Box-folder 191:003)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF WELFARE AND INSTITUTIONS BY WILLIAM LUKHARD, ET AL., 1975-1981, 1-TLS, 6-D, 1-TL (Box-folder 191:004)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF WELFARE AND INSTITUTIONS, 1967-1973, 9-D, 1-TL, 1-N (Box-folder 191:005)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF WELFARE AND INSTITUTIONS, 1961-1967, 1-TLS, 7-D (Box-folder 191:006)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF WELFARE AND INSTITUTIONS BY W.W. WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: RICHARD COPELAND, ET AL., 1956-1961, 25-D, 6-TL, 3-TLS, 3-AN, 2-N (Box-folder 191:007)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF WELFARE AND INSTITUTIONS, 1955-1956, 15-D, 4-pam, 2-N, 1-TL (Box-folder 191:008)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF WELFARE AND INSTITUTIONS, 1954-1955, 3-D, 12-pam, 1-TLS (Box-folder 191:009)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF WELFARE AND INSTITUTIONS BY ROBERT BARRIE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: MARY ALICE ROBERTS, ET AL, 1953-1954, 6-D, 1-TL, 1-TLS (Box-folder 191:010)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH X-RAY SCHEDULE BY W.W. WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: LOCAL ASSOCIATIONS, ET AL., 1953-1960, 6-D, 3-TLS, 1-N (Box-folder 191:011)
- STATE SANATORIA BY THOMAS MOAK, JR., ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: H.J. WEDDLE, ET AL., 1967-1969, 8-TL, 1-TLS, 19-D (Box-folder 192:001)
- STATE SECRETARIES CONFERENCE BY JAMES STONE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: EXECUTIVES OF CONSTITUENT ASSOCIATIONS, 1965-1968, 7-N, 7-D, 2-TL, 2-TLS (Box-folder 192:002)
- STATE SECRETARIES' CONFERENCE, 1964-1965, 8-D, 2-N, 1-TLS (Box-folder 192:003)
- STATE SECRETARIES CONFERENCE BY CLARISSA BOYD, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1964, 1-D, 1-TL, 2-TLS (Box-folder 192:004)
- STATE SECRETARIES MEETING BY LOUISE BAGLEY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: FRANCH LICK-SHERATON HOTEL, ET AL., 1963, 5-TL, 1-pam, 3-N, 2-TLS, 3-D, 1-AN (Box-folder 192:005)
- STATE SECRETARIES MEETING BY WILLIAM BIPPUS, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: JAMES STONE, ET AL., 1962, 2-D, 2-N, 1-TLS (Box-folder 192:006)
- STATE SECRETARIES MEETING BY JAMES PERKINS, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: EXECUTIVES OF CONSTITUENT ASSOCIATIONS,ET AL., 1955-1961, 11-N, 10-D, 4-TLS, 2-TL (Box-folder 192:007)
- STATE SECRETARIES CONFERENCE BY MR. STONE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: CONSTITUENT ASSOCIATIONS, ET AL., 1952-1955, 4-N, 17-D, 1-TL, 2-AN, 3-TLS (Box-folder 192:008)
- STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH--FEDERAL TUBERCULOSIS PROJECT BY WILLIAM APPERSON, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: J.B. KEGLEY, ET AL., 1969-1970, 1-TLS (Box-folder 192:009)
- STUDIES MADE BY VTRDA, 1940-1955, 3-D (Box-folder 192:010)
- SUPPLEMENTAL FUND RAISING BY HOWARD MANN, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: FRIEND, ET AL., 1974-1975, 1-TLS, 7-N, 14-D, 4-TL, 2-TLS, 1-ALS (Box-folder 192:011)
- STUDY OF TUBERCULOSIS IN VIRGINIA, SANATORIUMS, 1952, 23-D, 2-TLS, 5-map, 3-AD, 1-DS, 1-TL (Box-folder 193:001)
- STUDY OF TUBERCULOSIS IN VIRGINIA BY AMERICAN PUBLIC HEALTH ASSOCIATION, ET AL., 1952, 3-map, 4-N, 22-D (Box-folder 193:002)
- STUDY OF TUBERCULOSIS IN VIRGINIA BY R.L. SMITH, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: MEMBERS OF COMMITTEE FOR CONTROL OF TB, ET AL., 1952, 2-D (Box-folder 193:003)
- STUDY OF TUBERCULOSIS IN VIRGINIA BY J. LINDSAY ALMOND, JR./ADDRESSED TO: L.J. ROPER, ET AL., 1952, 21-D, 3-N, 4-TL (Box-folder 193:004)
- SUPPLY SERVICE BY DAVID KUSKIN, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1974-1978, 1-TLS, 4-N, 1-AD, 1-D (Box-folder 193:005)
- S--GENERAL BY THOMAS MOAK, JR., ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: JOSEPH SOKOLOWSKI, JR., ET AL., 1969-1976, 8-TL, 8-D, 3-N, 6-TLS, 5-DS (Box-folder 194:001)
- S--GENERAL BY MARY HELEN WILLIAMSON, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: WOODROW W. WENDT, ET AL., 1961-1967, 7-TLS, 14-D, 9-TL, 1-AN, 2-ALS, 3-N (Box-folder 194:002)
- TEACHERS WORKSHOP ON SMOKING AND HEALTH, 1980-1981, 1-AN, 1-N (Box-folder 194:003)
- TEACHER WORKSHOP ON SMOKING AND HEALTH BY FRANCES MAYS, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: VIRGINIA BLOCH, ET AL., 1979-1980, 9-D, 1-TLS, 2-TL (Box-folder 194:004)
- TEACHER WORKSHIP ON SMOKING AND HEALTH BY ALA, 1979-1980, 4-D (Box-folder 194:005)
- TEACHER TRAINING BY J.B. NICHOLLS, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: HAROLD MCGEE, ET AL., -1949, 2-TLS, 11-D, 3-N, 4-TL (Box-folder 194:006)
- TELEVISION BY NTA, 1952-1960, 3-N, 2-TLS, 1-TL, 13-D (Box-folder 194:007)
- TELEVISION BY W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1952-1957, 4-N, 1-TL, 12-D (Box-folder 194:008)
- TENNESSEE LUNG ASSOCIATION BY MS. PORTER,ET AL/ADDRESSED TO: MS. OSTWALD, ET AL., 1974-1975, 1-N, 3-D, 5-TLS, 6-TL (Box-folder 194:009)
- TENNESSEE TB-RD ASSOCIATION BY W.W WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: WILLIAM BUSSE, ET AL., 1971-1974, 2-TL, 2-TLS, 3-N, 1-D (Box-folder 194:010)
- TENNESSEE TUBERCULOSIS ASSOCIATION BY W.M. HARTNETT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: CATHARINE ZAHAROV, ET AL., 1958-1971, 8-TL, 11-TLS, 7-D, 1-pam (Box-folder 194:011)
- TREATMENT OF TUBERCULOSIS, -1949, 3-TL, 1-N, 34-D, 1-NEWSCLIP, 1-AN (Box-folder 195:001)
- TRI-STATE PROGRAM CONFERENCE, 1975, 2-D (Box-folder 195:002)
- TRI-STATE TUBERCULOSIS CONFERENCE ON PULMONARY DISEASES BY WILLIAM ANDERSON, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ALL COMMITTEE MEMBERS, ET AL., 1963-1971, 7-N, 14-D, 3-TL, 18-TLS (Box-folder 195:003)
- TRI-STATE TUBERCULOSIS CASE CONFERENCE BY DONALD BRUMMER, ET AL., 1960-1963, 6-TL, 22-D, 18-TLS, 1-AN, 3-N (Box-folder 195:004)
- TRI-STATE TUBERCULOSIS CASE CONFERENCE BY KARL PFUETZE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: WILLIAM APPERSON, ET AL., 1960, 3-TLS, 1-DS, 1-N, 3-D (Box-folder 195:005)
- VIRGINIA TRUDEAU SOCIETY--TRI-STATE TUBERCULOSIS CASE CONFERENCE BY W.W. WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: FILE, ET AL., 1955-1959, 5-N, 12-D, 7-TL, 7-TLS, 3-NEWSCLIPS (Box-folder 195:006)
- TRUDEAU, EDWARD L. AND THE AMERICAN TRUDEAU SOCIETY BY FRANK WEBSTER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: LESLIE FOSTER, ET AL., -1949, 4-pam, 4-photo, 11-TLS, 26-D, 2-N, 4-TL (Box-folder 195:007)
- VIRGINIA TRUDEAU SOCIETY--TRI STATE TUBERCULOSIS CASE CONFERENCE BY WILLIAM ANDERSON, ET AL., 1953-1954, 7-D, 2-TLS, 1-NEWSCLIP, 1-N (Box-folder 195:008)
- TUBERCULOSIS COMMITTEE BY CARL C. BOOBERG, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: CLIFTON PARKER, ET AL., 1980-1981, 5-D, 1-TLS, 1-AN, 1-N (Box-folder 195:009)
- TUBERCULOSIS COMMITTEE BY VLA, 1979-1980, 14-D, 5-TL, 1-TLS, 1-AN, 2-N (Box-folder 196:001)
- TUBERCULOSIS COMMITTEE BY VLA, 1977-1979, 8-D, 3-DS, 1-TLS, 1-AN (Box-folder 196:002)
- VIRGINIA LUNG ASSOCIATION--VTS TUBERCULOSIS COMMITTEE BY VLA-VTS, 1976-1977, 3-N, 4-D (Box-folder 196:003)
- TUBERCULOSIS--BOVINE (CATTLE) BY ALLEN KRAUSE, KENNETH DOWS, ET AL., -1949, 1-NEWSCLIP, 8-D, 1-TLS (Box-folder 196:004)
- TUBERCULOSIS ASSOCIATIONS SEAL SALES--CAMPAIGNS IN OTHER STATES BY RUTH MACMILLIAN, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: VTA, ET AL., -1949, 25-D, 1-NEWSCLIP, 29-TLS, 1-pam, 17-TL, 3-ALS, 1-N (Box-folder 196:005)
- TUBERCULOSIS ASSOCIATIONS SEAL SALES--CAMPAIGNS IN OTHER STATES BY ERNEST GRANT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: LESLIE FOSTER, ET AL., -1949, 39-D, 62-TLS, 3-ALS, 10-pam, 2-NEWSCLIPS, 21-TL, 7-N (Box-folder 196:006)
  2-AN
- TUBERCULOSIS ASSOCATIONS SEAL SALES--CAMPAIGNS IN OTHER STATES BY JACKSON, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: IRVING LEWIS SPEAR, ET AL., -1949, 1-NEWSCLIP, 1-AN, 35-D, 80-TLS, 35-TL, 19-N, 5-pam (Box-folder 196:007)
  2-ALS, 1-DS
- TUBERCULOSIS ASSOCATIONS SEAL SALES--CAMPAIGNS IN OTHER STATES BY IOWA TUBERCULOSIS ASSOCATION, ET AL., -1949, 48-D, 12-TL, 3-TLS, 3-N, 5-photos, 1-pam, 1-NEWSCLIP (Box-folder 197:001)
- TUBERCULOSIS-CASE FINDING, SURVEYS, CLINICS BY VTA, -1949, 1-TLS, 11-D (Box-folder 197:002)
- TUBERCULOSIS CASE FINDING--SURVEYS, CHEST CLINICS, SANATORIUMS, CONDITIONS OF CONTROL OF TUBERCULOSIS IN VIRGINIA BY VTA, -1949, 11-D (Box-folder 197:003)
- TUBERCULOSIS CASE FINDING--SURVEYS, CLINICS BY E.M. HOLMES, EMMETT MATHEWS, ET AL., -1949, 5-TLS, 3-N, 7-TL, 3-NEWSCLIP, 14-D (Box-folder 197:004)
- TUBERCULOSIS CONTROL BY VTA, -1949, 18-D (Box-folder 198:001)
- TUBERCULOSIS CHART SERIES BY U.S. DEPARTMENT OF PUBLIC HEALTH, EDUCATION, ET AL, -1949, 2-map, 3-D (Box-folder 198:002)
- TUBERCULOSIS CONTROL, -1949, 15-D, 1-NEWSCLIP (Box-folder 198:003)
- TUBERCULOSIS CONTROL, BLACK/AFRICAN AMERICAN PUBLIC HEALTH BY LOUISE STRACHAN, ET AL., -1949, 25-D, 1-TL, 2-TLS, 2-NEWSCLIPS (Box-folder 198:004)
  INCLUDES A WPA AND NEGRO HEALTH REPORT
- TUBERCULOSIS--FOREIGN COUNTRIES BY ASSISTANT SECRETARY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ANGES RANDOLPH, ET AL., -1949, 3-TLS, 2-TL (Box-folder 198:005)
- TUBERCULOSIS SOLDIERS BY ARTHUR TROLL, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: NATIONAL ASSOCIATION FOR PREVENTION TB, ET AL., -1949, 19-D, 20-TL, 2-DS, 8-ALS, 6-TLS, 16-AD, 7-AN, 1-NS (Box-folder 198:006)
- TUBERCULOSIS SOLDIERS, -1949, 22-TL, 14-D, 16-TLS, 2-N, 14-AD, 4-DS, 7-ALS (Box-folder 198:007)
- TUBERCULOSIS SOLDIERS, -1949, 2-NEWSCLIPS, 8-N, 21-D, 10-TL, 1-ANS, 4-TLS, 1-AD (Box-folder 198:008)
  1-PAM
- TUBERCULOSIS SOLDIERS BY PIEDMONT SANATORIUM, -1949, 25-TL, 19-D, 26-TLS, 1-AD (Box-folder 198:009)
- TUBERCULOSIS--THE DISEASE, BLACK/AFRICAN AMERICAN PUBLIC HEALTH BY WILLIAM WHITE, ET AL., -1949, 27-D, 4-NEWSCLIPS (Box-folder 199:001)
  INCLUDES--AN ADVENTURE IN FAITH--A BRIEF STORY OF THE INTERRACIAL MOVEMENT IN THE SOUTH
- TUBERCULOSIS--HISTORICAL DATA BY OHIO PUBLIC HEALTH, ET AL., -1949, 1-AD, 9-D, 6-NEWSCLIPS, 1-ALS, 1-c.d.s (Box-folder 199:002)
  INCLUDES A LETTER BY A MAN CLAIMING TO HAVE A NATURAL CURE FOR TUBERCULOSIS
- TUBERCULOSIS--DIAGNOSIS AND DIAGNOSTICAL STANDARDS, BLACK/AFRICAN AMERICAN PUBLIC HEALTH BY P.P. MCCAIN, ET AL., -1949, 1-N, 6-D, 1-NEWSCLIP (Box-folder 199:003)
- TUBERCULOSIS--DEATH RATES IN U.S., BLACK/AFRICAN AMERICAN PUBLIC HEALTH BY ISABEL MCCAFFREY, ET AL., -1949, 10-map, 2-chart, 1-N, 1-AN, 11-D (Box-folder 199:004)
  GIVES DESCRIPTIONS AND STATISTICS OF DISEASE ESPECIALLY GREAT TOLL ON AFRICAN AMERICANS
- TUBERCULOSIS DEATH RATES, BLACK/AFRICAN AMERICAN PUBLIC HEALTH, RACIAL EFFECTS OF TUBERCULOSIS BY NTA, -1949, 1-TLS, 2-N, 1-AN, 1-TL, 32-D, 2-NEWSCLIPS (Box-folder 199:005)
- TUBERCULOSIS DEATH RATES IN VIRGINIA BY VTA, -1949, 36-D, 1-NEWSCLIP, 1-N, 1-DS, 4-TLS (Box-folder 199:006)
- TUBERCULOSIS DEATH RATES IN VIRGINIA BY VTA, -1949, 86-D, 4-AN, 12-AD, 3-NEWSCLIPS, 2-N, 2-TLS (Box-folder 199:007)
- TB-RD HEALTH AWARD PROGRAM, 1968-1969, 4-D, 26-DS, 2-AN (Box-folder 200:001)
- TB-RD HEALTH AWARD PROGRAM BY W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1965-1967, 2-N, 6-D, 2-pam, 1-TLS, 2-TL, 1-DS (Box-folder 200:002)
- TUBERCULIN TESTING BY FRED BROECKER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: FRANCES MAYS, ET AL., 1963-1968, 2-NEWSCLIPS, 16-D, 3-TL, 3-TLS, 2-N (Box-folder 200:003)
- TUBERCULIN TESTING BY WILLIAM WAGNER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: LOCAL HEALTH DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1961-1963, 6-N, 1-pam, 2-ANS, 2-TLS, 12-D, 2-TL, 3-AN (Box-folder 200:004)
- TUBERCULIN TESTING BY DONALD TRAUGER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: NTA MEMBERS, ET AL., 1957-1961, 12-D, 1-TL, 1-N, 1-AD (Box-folder 200:005)
- TUBERCULIN TESTING BY CHARLES SHEPARD, ET AL., -1949, 34-D, 1-AN, 3-TL, 2-TLS, 1-NEWSCLIP (Box-folder 200:006)
- TB AUXILIARY OF NORFOLK BY H.W. AMBROSE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: CHARLES PEARSON, ET AL., 1960-1961, 2-NEWSCLIPS, 9-TLS, 4-D, 4-ALS, 9-TL, 1-AN (Box-folder 200:007)
- TUBERCULOSIS LABORATORY SERVICES BY VTBRDA, 1966, 1-D (Box-folder 200:008)
- TUBERCULOSIS GUIDANCE COMMITTEE BY VTRDA, 1970-1971, 19-D, 2-N, 1-TL (Box-folder 201:001)
- TUBERCULOSIS HOSPITAL STUDY, SANATORIUM USES WITH VACANT BEDS BY GORDON BURNETT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: MACK SHANHOLTZ, ET AL., 1963-1964, 18-D, 2-N, 5-NEWSCLIP, 1-TL, 1-TLS (Box-folder 201:002)
- TUBERCULOSIS HOSPITAL STUDY BY E.C. DRASH, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: MEMBERS OF TB HOSPITAL STUDY COMMITTEE, ET AL., 1963-1964, 7-D, 8-N, 1-TL (Box-folder 201:003)
- TUBERCULOSIS HOSPITAL STUDY, SANATORIUMS BY FREDERICK BROECKER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1962, 13-D, 4-AD, 10-N, 3-TLS, 7-TL (Box-folder 201:004)
- TUBERCULOSIS FOUNDATION OF VIRGINIA BY HAROLD MCGEE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.B. CARTER, ET AL., 1954-1955, 2-TL, 1-ALS, 1-NEWSCLIPS (Box-folder 201:005)
- TUBERCULOSIS BY THOMAS MOAK, JR., ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: WILLIAM E. APPERSON, ET AL., 1958-1960;1970-1979, 13-D, 1-TL, 5-NEWSCLIP, 1-TLS (Box-folder 201:006)
- TUBERCULOSIS BY VTA, 1963-1975, 13-D, 1-TLS, 5-NEWSCLIP, 3-TL, 2-N (Box-folder 201:007)
- TUBERCULOSIS, 1962-1963, 2-D (Box-folder 201:008)
- TUBERCULOSIS BY MYRON MILLER, ET AL., 1954-1962, 31-D, 25-NEWSCLIP, 1-TL, 1-TLS, 1-AD, 1-N, 1-pam, 1-c.d (Box-folder 201:009)
- TUBERCULOSIS, 1953-1954, 12-NEWSCLIP, 13-D, 1-TL (Box-folder 202:001)
- TUBERCULOSIS BY VTA, 1952-1953, 2-NEWSCLIP, 27-D, 1-TL (Box-folder 202:002)
- TUBERCULOSIS MENINGITIS PROPHYSLAXIS STUDY BY FLOYD FELDMANN, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: HAROLD MCGEE, ET AL., 1954-1957, 5-TLS, 1-TL, 5-D, 1-N (Box-folder 202:003)
- TUBERCULOSIS VIRGINIA BY VTA, 1955-1957; 1960-1961, 2-pam, 26-D, 1-NEWSCLIP, 4-N (Box-folder 202:004)
- TUBERCULOSIS BY STATISTICAL SERVICE, NTA, ET AL., 1952-1954, 28-D, 1-AN, 9-NEWSCLIPS (Box-folder 202:005)
- TUBERCULOSIS BY U.S. DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH AND HUMAN SERVICES,ET AL, 1979-1981, 7-D (Box-folder 202:006)
- T--GENERAL, 1951-1981, 18-D, 21-TLS, 6-N, 17-TL, 2-pam, 1-AN, 1-NEWSCLIP (Box-folder 202:007)
- UNITED FUND BY MR. KEHOE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: CONSTITUENT COMMITTEES, ET AL., 1956-1966, 3-D, 5-N, 1-TL (Box-folder 202:008)
- UNITED BUSINESS SERVICE BY PAUL TALBOT, JR., ET AL., 1958-1959, 12-D, 2-TLS (Box-folder 202:009)
- UNITED FUND CAMPAIGN, 1957-1958, 14-D, 1-TL (Box-folder 203:001)
- UNITED FUND BY NTA, 1956-1957, 9-D, 1-N, 1-NEWSCLIP, 1-TL (Box-folder 203:002)